<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio website of Fabian Sinn</title>
    <link>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Portfolio website of Fabian Sinn</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:42:51 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Coming soon.</title>
      <link>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/blogs/aliquam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:42:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/blogs/aliquam/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R MarkdownThis is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars)## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/pages/about_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/pages/about_me/</guid>
      <description>I’m an Analytics and Management (MAM) student at London Business School (2021) currently on my educational leave from Bain &amp;amp; Company. I’m strongly interested in the intersection of technology and management with a focus on data analytics and behavioral biometrics. During my time at Bain, I gained experience in commercial diligence work as part of the Private Equity Group as well as Customer Experience (NPS) transformation.
Being a Business Graduate from the University of Mannheim, I was part of the IBEA program studying at ESSEC Business School (Singapore), FGV EBAPE (Rio de Janeiro), and Darla Moore School of Business (Columbia).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AirBnB Beijing (Part 1)</title>
      <link>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/pages/airbnb_beijing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/pages/airbnb_beijing/</guid>
      <description>Introduction (Part 1: Data cleaning + EDA)The following project focuses on the analysis of an AirBnB dataset. As part of the project I performed Exploratory Data Analysis (EDA), Data visualization as well as Regression Analysis. The final output is a multivariate regression model that predicts the total cost of two people to stay at an AirBnB property in Beijing for 4 nights. For the purpose of this work display I’ll present a smaller subset of analyses and visualizations that were part of the larger project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data visualization in R</title>
      <link>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/pages/data-visualization-in-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/pages/data-visualization-in-r/</guid>
      <description>IntroductionIn our data driven world the visualization of data is an essential skill in order to transport meaningful messages. It allows us to go beyond the mere analysis of data for the sake of analysis. The following collection of visualizations in R using ggplot are a representation of my work at London Business School in the process of enhancing my skills in the field. I will regularly add new visualizations going forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Social Survey</title>
      <link>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/pages/gss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/pages/gss/</guid>
      <description>IntroductionThe General Social Survey (GSS) gathers data on American society in order to monitor and explain trends in attitudes, behaviours, and attributes. Many trends have been tracked for decades, so one can see the evolution of attitudes, etc in American Society.
The General Social SurveyIn the following section we will use the GSS survey data sample to predict population parameters for people’s social media usage.We will be creating 95% confidence intervals for population parameters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London Bikeshare Data</title>
      <link>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/pages/bikeshare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/pages/bikeshare/</guid>
      <description>Introduction[…]
“The ability to visualize data in a meaningful way keeps us focused on the ‘So what?!’ of our analysis.”
[…]In the following section we will visualize the 2016 Brexit vote data in the UK. Specifically, we show how the political addiliation int he 2015 UK general election translated into Brexit voting.
The data[…]
The processFirst, we load the dataframe…
#brexit_results &amp;lt;- read_csv(here::here(&amp;quot;data&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;XXX&amp;quot;))Let’s have a look at the dataframe…</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>