<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Portfolio website of Fabian Sinn</title>
    <link>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Portfolio website of Fabian Sinn</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/pages/about_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/pages/about_me/</guid>
      <description>I’m an Analytics and Management (MAM) student at London Business School (2021) currently on my educational leave from Bain &amp;amp; Company. I’m strongly interested in the intersection of technology and management with a focus on data analytics and behavioral biometrics. During my time at Bain, I gained experience in commercial diligence work as part of the Private Equity Group as well as Customer Experience (NPS) transformation.
Being a Business Graduate from the University of Mannheim, I was part of the IBEA program studying at ESSEC Business School (Singapore), FGV EBAPE (Rio de Janeiro), and Darla Moore School of Business (Columbia).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data visualization in R</title>
      <link>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/pages/data-visualization-in-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabiansinn.netlify.app/pages/data-visualization-in-r/</guid>
      <description>IntroductionIn our data driven world the visualization of data is an essential skill in order to transport meaningful messages. It allows us to go beyond the mere analysis of data for the sake of analysis. The following collection of visualizations in R using ggplot are a representation of my work at London Business School in the process of enhancing my skills in the field. I will regularly add new visualizations going forward.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>